Frank J. Becker Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Correspondence, 1953-1964; nam_apap224-2; 2.4 cubic ft.
  - Immigration, E, 1957; nam_apap224-2_41 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Immigration, E, 1959; nam_apap224-2_42 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Immigration, E, 1961; nam_apap224-2_43 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Immigration, E, 1962; nam_apap224-2_44 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Immigration, E, 1963; nam_apap224-2_45 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Immigration, F, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_46 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Immigration, F, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_47 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Immigration, F, 1955-1960; nam_apap224-2_48 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Immigration, F, 1956-1957; nam_apap224-2_49 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Immigration, F, 1961; nam_apap224-2_50 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Immigration, F, 1962; nam_apap224-2_51 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Immigration, F, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_52 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Immigration G, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_53 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Immigration G, 1954-1957; nam_apap224-2_54 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Immigration G, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_55 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Immigration, G, 1958; nam_apap224-2_56 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Immigration, G, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_57 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Immigration, G, 1961; nam_apap224-2_58 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Immigration, G, 1962; nam_apap224-2_59 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Immigration, G, 1963; nam_apap224-2_60 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Immigration, H, 1954; nam_apap224-2_61 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Immigration, H, 1954-1958; nam_apap224-2_62 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Immigration, H, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_63 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Immigration, H, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_64 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Immigration, H, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_65 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Immigration, H, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_66 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Immigration, H, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_67 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Immigration, I, 1953; nam_apap224-2_68 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Immigration, I, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_69 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, I, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_70 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Immigration, I, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_71 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Immigration, I, 1960-1962; nam_apap224-2_72 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Immigration, I, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_73 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Immigration, J, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_74 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Immigration, J, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_75 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Immigration, J, 1960; nam_apap224-2_76 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Immigration, J, 1961-1964; nam_apap224-2_77 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Immigration, J, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_78 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Immigration, K, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_79 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Immigration, K, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_80 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Immigration, K, 1955-1957; nam_apap224-2_81 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Immigration, K, 1958; nam_apap224-2_82 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Immigration, K, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_83 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Immigration, K, 1960-1962; nam_apap224-2_84 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Immigration, K, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_85 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Immigration, L, 1953; nam_apap224-2_86 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Immigration, L, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_87 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Immigration, L, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_88 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Immigration, L, 1959-1962; nam_apap224-2_89 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Immigration,L, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_90 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Immigration, Lan, Hom Tew, Wong Kwong, Svey, Wong, 1958-1960; nam_apap224-2_91 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Immigration, M, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_92 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Immigration, M, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_93 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Immigration, M, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_94 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Immigration, M, 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_95 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Immigration, M, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_96 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Immigration, M, 1961; nam_apap224-2_97 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Immigration, M, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_98 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Immigration, M, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_99 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Immigration, Mc, 1955; nam_apap224-2_100 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Immigration, Mc, 1958; nam_apap224-2_101 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Immigration, Mc, 1960; nam_apap224-2_102 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Immigration, Mc, 1964; nam_apap224-2_103 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Immigration, N, 1953; nam_apap224-2_104 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Immigration, N, 1954-1955; nam_apap224-2_105 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Immigration, N, 1956-1958; nam_apap224-2_106 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, N, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_107 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Immigration, N, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_108 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Immigration, Naturalization (Congratulatory Letters), 1961; nam_apap224-2_109 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Immigration, Naturalization (Congratulatory Letters), 1962; nam_apap224-2_110 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Immigration, Naturalization - Citizens, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_111 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Immigration, O, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_112 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Immigration, O, 1955-1958; nam_apap224-2_113 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Immigration, O, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_114 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Immigration, O, 1960; nam_apap224-2_115 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Immigration, O, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_116 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Immigration, O, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_117 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Immigration, P, 1952-1955; nam_apap224-2_118 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Immigration, P, 1956; nam_apap224-2_119 (Box 4, Folder 0)
  - Immigration, P, 1957; nam_apap224-2_120 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Immigration, P, 1958; nam_apap224-2_121 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Immigration, P, 1959; nam_apap224-2_122 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Immigration, P, 1960; nam_apap224-2_123 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Immigration, P, 1961; nam_apap224-2_124 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Immigration, P, 1962; nam_apap224-2_125 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Immigration, P, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_126 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Immigration, Q, 1962; nam_apap224-2_127 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Immigration, Q, 1962-1963; nam_apap224-2_128 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Immigration, R, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_129 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Immigration, R, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_130 (Box 5, Folder 0)
  - Immigration, R, 1956-1958; nam_apap224-2_131 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Immigration, R, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_132 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Immigration, R, 1960-1962; nam_apap224-2_133 (Box 5, Folder 0)
  - Immigration, R, 1962-1964; nam_apap224-2_134 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, Riccio, Raffaele, 1958-1960; nam_apap224-2_135 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Immigration, S, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_136 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Immigration, S, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_137 (Box 5, Folder 0)
  - Immigration,S, 1957; nam_apap224-2_138 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Immigration,S, 1958; nam_apap224-2_139 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Immigration,S, 1959; nam_apap224-2_140 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Immigration, S, 1960; nam_apap224-2_141 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Immigration, S, 1961; nam_apap224-2_142 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Immigration, S, 1962; nam_apap224-2_143 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Immigration, S, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_144 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Immigration, T, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_145 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Immigration, T, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_146 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Immigration, T, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_147 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Immigration, T, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_148 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Immigration, T, 1961; nam_apap224-2_149 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Immigration, T, 1962; nam_apap224-2_150 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Immigration, T, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_151 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Immigration, V, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_152 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Immigration, V, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_153 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Immigration, V, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_154 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, V, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_155 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Immigration, V, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_156 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Immigration, V, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_157 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Immigration, W, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_158 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Immigration, W, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_159 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Immigration, W, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_160 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Immigration, W, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_161 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Immigration, W, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_162 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Immigration, W, 1962-1964; nam_apap224-2_163 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Immigration, Y, 1955; nam_apap224-2_164 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Immigration, Y, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_165 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Immigration, Y, 1961; nam_apap224-2_166 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Immigration, Y, 1964; nam_apap224-2_167 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Immigration, Z, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_168 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Immigration, Z, 1954-1956; nam_apap224-2_169 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Immigration, Z, 1957; nam_apap224-2_170 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Immigration, Z, 1958-1960; nam_apap224-2_171 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Immigration, Z, 1962; nam_apap224-2_172 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Immigration, Z, 1962-1963; nam_apap224-2_173 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Servicemen, A, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_174 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Servicemen, A, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_175 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Servicemen, A, 1958; nam_apap224-2_176 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Servicemen, A, 1959; nam_apap224-2_177 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Servicemen, A, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_178 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Servicemen, A, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_179 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Servicemen, A, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_180 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, B, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_181 (Box 7, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, B, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_182 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, B, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_183 (Box 7, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, B, 1960; nam_apap224-2_184 (Box 7, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, B, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_185 (Box 7, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, B, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_186 (Box 7, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Bejarano, Luis, 1960-1962; nam_apap224-2_187 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, C, 1952-1954; nam_apap224-2_188 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, C, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_189 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, C, 1957; nam_apap224-2_190 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, C, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_191 (Box 8, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, C, 1959; nam_apap224-2_192 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, C, 1960; nam_apap224-2_193 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, C, 1961; nam_apap224-2_194 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, C, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_195 (Box 8, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, C, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_196 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, Caputo, John J., 1951-1956; nam_apap224-2_197 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, Crownfield, Eleanor, 1959-1962; nam_apap224-2_198 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, D, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_199 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, D, 1955; nam_apap224-2_200 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, D, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_201 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, D, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_202 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, D, 1960; nam_apap224-2_203 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, D, 1961; nam_apap224-2_204 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, D, 1962; nam_apap224-2_205 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, D, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_206 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, Dragstedt, Carl, 1958; nam_apap224-2_207 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, E, 1952-1953; nam_apap224-2_208 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, E, 1954-1956; nam_apap224-2_209 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Servicemen, E, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_210 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, E, 1959; nam_apap224-2_211 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, E, 1960; nam_apap224-2_212 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, E, 1961; nam_apap224-2_213 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, E, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_214 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, E, 1963; nam_apap224-2_215 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, F, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_216 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, F, 1956; nam_apap224-2_217 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, F, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_218 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, F, 1960; nam_apap224-2_219 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, F, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_220 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, F, 1962; nam_apap224-2_221 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, F, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_222 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, Farrell, Stanley, 1962-1963; nam_apap224-2_223 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, G, 1954; nam_apap224-2_224 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, G, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_225 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, G, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_226 (Box 9, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, G, 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_227 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, G, 1960; nam_apap224-2_228 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, G, 1961; nam_apap224-2_229 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, G, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_230 (Box 9, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, G, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_231 (Box 9, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, H, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_232 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, H, 1955; nam_apap224-2_233 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, H, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_234 (Box 10, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, H, 1959; nam_apap224-2_235 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, H, 1960; nam_apap224-2_236 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, H, 1961; nam_apap224-2_237 (Box 10, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, H, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_238 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, H, 1962-1964; nam_apap224-2_239 (Box 10, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Huber, Erwin W., 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_240 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, I, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_241 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, I, 1959; nam_apap224-2_242 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, I, 1961; nam_apap224-2_243 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, J, 1953; nam_apap224-2_244 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, J, 1954-1955; nam_apap224-2_245 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, J, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_246 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, J, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_247 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, J, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_248 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, J, 1963; nam_apap224-2_249 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, K, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_250 (Box 10, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, K, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_251 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Servicemen, K, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_252 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Servicemen, K, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_253 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Servicemen, K, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_254 (Box 10, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, K, 1960-1962; nam_apap224-2_255 (Box 10, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, K, 1962-1964; nam_apap224-2_256 (Box 10, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, L, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_257 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, L, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_258 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, L, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_259 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, L, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_260 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, L, 1961; nam_apap224-2_261 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, L, 1962; nam_apap224-2_262 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, L, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_263 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, Lavale, Ronald, 1956-1958; nam_apap224-2_264 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, M, 1952-1954; nam_apap224-2_265 (Box 11, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, M, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_266 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, M, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_267 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, M, 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_268 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, M, 1960; nam_apap224-2_269 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, M, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_270 (Box 11, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, M, 1962; nam_apap224-2_271 (Box 11, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, M, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_272 (Box 11, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_273 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_274 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_275 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_276 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_277 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, N, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_278 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, N, 1956-1958; nam_apap224-2_279 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, N, 1960; nam_apap224-2_280 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, N, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_281 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, N, 1962-1964; nam_apap224-2_282 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, Navey, Edwin, 1958; nam_apap224-2_283 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, Nystrom, J, 1962; nam_apap224-2_284 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, O, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_285 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, O, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_286 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, O, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_287 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, O, 1960; nam_apap224-2_288 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, O, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_289 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, O, 1962-1963; nam_apap224-2_290 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, P, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_291 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, P, 1954-1956; nam_apap224-2_292 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, P, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_293 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, P, 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_294 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Servicemen, P, 1960; nam_apap224-2_295 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Servicemen, P, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_296 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Servicemen, P, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_297 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Servicemen, P, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_298 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Servicemen, Pappas, James, 1960-1963; nam_apap224-2_299 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Servicemen, Pilkington, Marines, 1964; nam_apap224-2_300 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Servicemen, Q, 1956-1957; nam_apap224-2_301 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Servicemen, Q, 1957; nam_apap224-2_302 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Servicemen, R, 1952-1954; nam_apap224-2_303 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Servicemen, R, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_304 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Servicemen, R, 1956-1958; nam_apap224-2_305 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Servicemen, R, 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_306 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Servicemen, R, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_307 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Servicemen, R, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_308 (Box 13, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, R, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_309 (Box 13, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, R, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_310 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, S, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_311 (Box 13, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_312 (Box 13, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_313 (Box 13, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1959; nam_apap224-2_314 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, S, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_315 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, S, 1960; nam_apap224-2_316 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, S, 1961; nam_apap224-2_317 (Box 13, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_318 (Box 13, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_319 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Servicemen, S, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_320 (Box 14, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Simons, Robert P., 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_321 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, Simons, Marshall, 1951-1954; nam_apap224-2_322 (Box 14, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Sternberg, Alan - [RESTRICTED], 1955-1958; 1960-1962; nam_apap224-2_323 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, T, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_324 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, T, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_325 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, T, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_326 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, T, 1958-1960; nam_apap224-2_327 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, T, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_328 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, T, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_329 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, T, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_330 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, Trop, Albert L., 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_331 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, U, 1954; nam_apap224-2_332 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, 1958; nam_apap224-2_333 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, U, 1959; nam_apap224-2_334 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, U, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_335 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, U, 1963; nam_apap224-2_336 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, V, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_337 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, V, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_338 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, V, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_339 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Servicemen, V, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_340 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Servicemen, V, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_341 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Servicemen, V, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_342 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Servicemen, W, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_343 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Servicemen, W, 1955-1957; nam_apap224-2_344 (Box 14, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, W, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_345 (Box 14, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, W, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_346 (Box 14, Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, W, 1961; nam_apap224-2_347 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, W, 1962; nam_apap224-2_348 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, W, 1963; nam_apap224-2_349 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, Weston, Doctor George M., 1955; 1957; nam_apap224-2_350 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, Woltin, Carl, 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_351 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, Y, 1958; nam_apap224-2_352 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, Y, 1959; nam_apap224-2_353 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, Y, 1962; nam_apap224-2_354 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1952-1953; nam_apap224-2_355 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1955; nam_apap224-2_356 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1958; nam_apap224-2_357 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_358 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_359 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1964; nam_apap224-2_360 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Veterans, A, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_361 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Veterans, A, 1960; nam_apap224-2_362 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Veterans, A, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_363 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Veterans, A, 1963; nam_apap224-2_364 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Veterans, Avidon, Samuel, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_365 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Veterans, B, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_366 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Veterans, B, 1956-1958; nam_apap224-2_367 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Veterans, B, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_368 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Veterans, B, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_369 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Veterans, B, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_370 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Veterans, Bartels, Robert, 1954; nam_apap224-2_371 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Veterans, Bates, Richard Paul, 1951-1953; nam_apap224-2_372 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Veterans, Buchan, Herbert J, 1954; nam_apap224-2_373 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Veterans, Budischak, Steve G., 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_374 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Veterans, C, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_375 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Veterans, C, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_376 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Veterans, C, 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_377 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Veterans, C, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-2_378 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Veterans, C, 1961; nam_apap224-2_379 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Veterans, C, 1962; nam_apap224-2_380 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Veterans, C, 1964; nam_apap224-2_381 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Veterans, Cain, Nelson A., 1953; nam_apap224-2_382 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Veterans, Clement, Emil, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_383 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Veterans, Columbine, Henry F., 1954; nam_apap224-2_384 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Veterans, Columbine, Robert L., 1953; nam_apap224-2_385 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Veterans, Comentino, Frank L., 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_386 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Veterans, Cromwell, Herbert J., 1953; nam_apap224-2_387 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Veterans, D, 1954; nam_apap224-2_388 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Veterans, D, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_389 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Veterans, D, 1957; nam_apap224-2_390 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Veterans, D, 1959; nam_apap224-2_391 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Veterans, D, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_392 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Veterans, D, 1963; nam_apap224-2_393 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Veterans, Dorf, Alfred L., 1958-1959; nam_apap224-2_394 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Veterans, E, 1954; nam_apap224-2_395 (Box 15, Folder 49)